Hello.
Great.
I am from the city of Khmelnitsky.  My name is
Andrey.  Where are you from?
Moscow.   What's
your name?
Nikita.  Holy [ __ ].  Khmelnitsky.  What do
you have written?  Norperm Eurasia 2 3.
Nor Perm, yes.  Normpermi Eurasia.   What is this
?   What's
bothering you?
Nunorperm Eurasia.  Norpem
Eurasia Map.
What are you talking about, Nikitos?  I want
to earn a million dollars.
What do you want?
A million dollars.
Cool.  What options do you have to
earn a million bucks?  If I
had options, I would be sitting here, yes.
I probably wouldn't be sitting here.
No, well, maybe, maybe these options are
not feasible.  Well, what ideas do
you have?   There are
no ideas at all.  Zero.  I'm telling you,
if I had ideas, I wouldn't be sitting here.
Tell me, do
you know what money is?
What is money?
Yeah, I
know.
Well, tell me,
what should I tell you?
Well, what is money?
Money is power.
Not specifically.  What is money?  Money.   He
who prints money rules the
world.
M.A, that is, other slaves, right?  There is a master,
there is a slave.
Well, yes, yes.
So, you're a slave?
No, I print money.
You print money and sit in
chat roulette.   Are
you kidding?  [clears throat]
Why?  I'm entertaining myself here,
watching my slaves, how they try to send me money
.
For what?
Well, if you don't print money, then you
print a lot of money,
right?  That's why I won't send you anything.
Why did you send it?  I'll say one very smart
thing.  What is money?
Ah, well, come on.   In
small print, in small, small print,
they printed out what money was.  Soviet
compensation obligations.  Ticket, yes,
you'll talk now.
Oh, no, no, no, not an obligation.  No,
tell me word for word what was
written there.
USSR Bank Note.  Oh,
and you have it written as a banknote from the Bank of Russia, but on
the hryvnias it doesn’t say that it’s a banknote from the Bank of
Ukraine,
because they’re the ones looking for it.  Do you understand
what I'm talking about?   Do
you understand what I'm talking about?
Didn't understand.   Now
I'll repeat again what you
said.
Well, a bank note from the Bank of Russia.  Yes.   Yes.  What does that mean
?  Well, just a bank note.   So.  A
bank note is printed.  Yes.  Which one?
Russia.  Not Russia.
Well, it's like a theater, right?  It's like a
theater ticket, right?  You're doing great.  What the
[ __ ], do you even understand a little bit?  Well, just a little bit
.  Well, of course, you have genetics.
I, look, I, I understand all this.  That's
why I understood everything a long time ago.  And I print
these tickets.
You see, you lived as a pauper, a
pauper.  Mark my words.  You
will never make a lot of
money.  Never.  You know, [snorts]
why?
Why?
Well, you have no thoughts, no, none.
The fact that you think you're so smart means that
people there will start transferring money to you
, right?  There will be no money.  What he
will transfer to you is pennies.
Money is the ticket.  Tickets.
You yourself said it was a ticket.  It wasn't me who
said that word, mind you.
Well, now think about what a ticket is.
There is a ticket for the tram and the bus.
Yes, a ticket for some services, for entry.
Yes, yes, yes.  You provide some services.
You are not doing any service to any bank.
I am nothing.  I just print these tickets.
I am a counterfeit coiner.
Oh, a fake mannequin is a completely
different thing.
Fake ticket seller.  I am a fake
ticket holder.
Now
you yourself have already admitted that you are here.
Explain,
I'm explaining to you.
Well, you know, I told you
about what is official, what a ticket is.
You're starting me, I'm a fake dummie.  I
say, just imagine, you are a banker, the
main banker.  Not even just a banker,
but the head of the Central Bank is definitely the
main one there.  What do you do with the money?   I'm typing
.
So what do you do next?
I lend them out to other people.
Oh, you're starting to think, huh?  Well, you have some
brains there, like from a collective farm,
right?  That's why you don't understand where to
distribute what from, to whom to distribute it, and what to
distribute.  That's why he told the chamois to give it away
.  No, no, let's just forget this
word specifically.  Look, [clears throat]
you're the boss.
Well, in the Central Bank, like you, I don’t know what you
call it there.
Who is the main one in your economy there?
Are you from Russia?  Well, who is the main one from Russia
?
Nabiullina.
Elvira.
Elvira Nabiullina.
Okay, let's say so.
And what does she do?
prints rubles,
sets the key rate.
Well
and
and what
next?
And
I don't understand this so much.  I really don't have enough
intelligence to explain it.
So you understand, it's genetics.  You
explain genetics to me, genetically speaking, right?
Fine.
[sighs][snorts]
The second example from America, yes, in the center of
New York there is such a board.
Federal Reserve, right?   Yes.
It's not they who owe the
debt there, right?  America's debt, huh?
Duty.  Here.
Now think about it.  Do you have a printer?   A
printer that prints money.  I'll
even give you a hint, as you understand, these people
understand, the one there. Well, okay, just don't
be offended.  Well, you're your mother, I'll
just oblige.  Okay,
explain the solution.  Yes, explain,
wait, wait, wait, just
explain.  I understand that this is just my
genetics.  I see you are the pinnacle of
evolution, right?  Explain to me what's going on in
New York.
Printer.  A printer that prints
money.  Just imagine this.  You have
children, you have a mother,
yes, but there is the Federal Reserve
System.
Wait, let me ask the question.  [laughter]
Federal Reserve System.  Okay,
wait.  And what does it mean federally?  Not federal.   Give it to
me.  Wait, come on.   What does the
ticket have to do with it?
Later.  Wait for me, 2 minutes,
[ __ ].  Here are 2 minutes, give me a minute to
speak.  Give me one minute to speak.
Okay, give me 30 seconds to speak.  You'll give
me 30 seconds to speak.
Let's.
You have a printer.  Just like in America,
right?  And you take it, and this debt is like that
.  What does Biulina have to do with this?
Yes, I say, forget about Biulina.  I go like this
.  What does an American printer have to do with it, if it's
on Biulina?  I can't understand.
Then you will understand.  You will understand.   That's
it, we'll let you through to Biulina.  Understood.
You have a printer, you print
dollars, imagine, just not dollars, but
tickets.  No,
no, I get it, I get it.
Bank of America tickets.
No,
they are also Ameri Bank notes.  What is
written?  No no no no in Dast.  What is
written on some dollar bills?
In God we trust.
Well, you almost guessed it.  The all-seeing eye is still
written there.   Well done,
this guy.  Well, I said it wrong.
Okay, I forgive you for that.  Look,
in short, they want the dollar to be
everywhere in the world.  If I print dollars,
well, let's say, well
, wait.  By the way, I'm
confused.  What do the Bank
of Russia notes
you're talking about have to do with this?
I didn't quite understand.
Calm down.  Oh, wait, let me speak for
one minute.
Yes, I understand.  Just explain why
tickets and America.
I'm trying to explain it to you now.  Well, I
understand that you do
n't have the brains that I do.  I can't
understand.  Link tickets of the Russia
America bank.  Listen, you see,
your brain is starting to think.  Well done,
well done, well done.  This is where
my inner Google kicked in.   Okay
, stop.  That's it, yes, good, go ahead and
tell me.
Look, you have a printer that
prints.  Well, I'm exaggerating.
Well, this is not a printer, it is a resograph.  The word
faster faster.   The
Russian word is exaggerated.  What's happened?
What does exaggerated mean?  Don't know.
Russian is not my native language.
In short, the word "exaggerated" in Russian
means simple.   It's just a
simple printer.   So.   Yes.  I
myself don’t know what the word “
exaggerated” means.  No, that means exaggerated, in
my opinion.  Yes.  This is not a problem.
I don't know.  You were the one who
came up with this word?
Yes, I just exaggerated it.  I don't
know what the word exaggerated
means.  Forget it.
The word morning is exaggerated.  I was wrong.
Exaggeratedly - it's morning, early.
Not exaggerated is when you simply
explain.
Well, it's like this, it's just from the word morning.
The morning is exaggerated, the evening is evening.   He'll
dig in.   There's something wrong with my
brain, I guess, yes.
Exaggerated is not exaggerated.  No,
maybe just, damn.  You didn't
tell me about this printer.
Ah,
I get it.  In short, you, well, just
imagine, well, I understand that your
brain is so intimidated there, right?
Come on, come on, yes.  You're signing me up, yeah,
in short, it's
all about money, it's a bluff.  Look,
you have a printer, right?  You print
money.  I'll just explain it briefly now
quickly, otherwise something will happen to you.  You
switched, by the way.  I didn't get involved.
In short, you print money.
Well, you print money, right?
Nobody needs them.
Nobody needed them.
Money or bank notes?
Money.
Money.  What about bank notes?
There are money tickets in the bank.
Same.  Listen, wait, [clears throat]
relax.  Listen, you print, you
need to make these papers just not tickets,
okay, not money, just printed pieces of paper
.  You need to make them
liquid, exaggeratedly liquid.  You need to
make them liquid.
So you're saying this in an exaggerated way?   Yes.
Exaggerated.
And here is the word.  What does exaggerated mean?
What does exaggerated mean?  Reminded me of the word
exaggerated.  What did I think the word meant, what does the
word exaggerated mean?
I didn't understand either.  I think that
this is exaggerated, I myself have not forgotten that the word
exaggerated refers to something
exaggerated.
What does the word "exaggerated" mean?
Excessively exaggerated strong
distortion or emphasis on one particular
detail.  On the contrary, it is too
distorted
and emphasizes one detail to the detriment of the
others.
I didn't even know myself, naturally.  I
just said it was really required.  I did
n’t know what I was talking about, I didn’t even remember that word.
Something's just wrong with my brain about this.
I understand.  So, well, so the printer.  What's
next?
Well, you know, well [clears throat]
according to logic, just your logic.  Well,
why would America need to borrow money
if America prints money?
For what?
And who then?  When does America owe money to whom
?
Well, the Chinese take the base.
Well, have you seen America's national debt?
I saw.  There's always this on the sign on this
street
in New York.
Well, yes, the street is what's it called?
Bryan Bech.
No, I don't think it's Brian, I think it's a
different street.  No, another street.  Well, I
was walking around, in short, which street is the main one.
That scoreboard there is different.  Don't take the whip.  No,
no,
there's another street, I forgot.  This street there is
another street, not another street.  The scoreboard is a
cheat.  In short, the meaning is different.   Yes.
For what?  Even in Japan, and Japan,
by the way, took out a debt from America.  And
America, yes, well, dropped an atomic bomb
on the Japanese.
By the way, I checked it on Wikipedia, and the Japanese
sue America every year because they still have
food-borne diseases there.  Well, it’s
not sanctions and these, what’s it called, reparations.
Well, what first day, yes, only
the Russians didn’t leave, they came in on the twenty-fourth, and on the
twenty-fifth he’s already saying: “You
owe us reparations.”  And the Japanese, well, it’s clear
that they are still paying reparations.  Well,
these are not Russians, right?  It’s not that
reparations are paid immediately, even from the first day.  Somehow
you also
already owe portions.  Gosdol,
wait, the same thing happens with the Japanese
.
US national debt.  What does this have to do with it?  Don't
jump on the Japanese.  State debt and printing
printer.  Well, don't exaggerate, let's get straight to the
point.
Well,
well, printer.
Well, for what?  take up debt.
What a sprinter.  What are you talking about?  And
so I also think, why would I go through
something kupo.  You have a printer, you
print money and you take your neighbor.
You say: "Neighbor, give me money, listen,
dollars."  And you have a printer that
prints dollars.  Why then
?  How can the US be in debt if
they have a printer?
I am explaining this to you, why this is
done.
I'm explaining this to you.  Why
do this?  If they don't do it, then it's
dollar
for dollar.
If they take on dollar debt, then the
dollar will be worth the money,
so they can simply print dollars
instead of taking on dollar debt.   I ca
n't understand why.  Look, if
I had a printer that printed
money, why would I take out a loan from the bank
if I could print dollars?
In short, it wasn’t [laughter] that
they fried him a second time.
Like, subscribe, comment.  Subscribe to
our WhatsApp channel.  Here is the QR code.  There,
news similar to that
in the Telegram channel is posted for those who don’t have
Telegram or who don’t use it for
other reasons.  Subscribe to our
WhatsApp channel.  M.